o-re-sa-ma.com 2013-03-07

# 

**About the handling of this fan club's personal information (privacy policy)**

* * *

**[Management subject]**  
Management of this fan club is a "fan cube", and manages based on the handling of the following personal information (privacy policy).

* * *

**[The purpose of use]**  
For healthy management of a fan club, this fan club uses a member's personal information, as shown below. Moreover, this use is aimed at protecting a member's profits.   
◎ Procedure in connection with fan club office work, such as admission and updating   
◎ a member -- change of the member information by the proposal of the person himself/herself   
◎ Dispatch of a privilege of membership and a report   
◎ Goods sale and its dispatch   
◎ Ticket sale and its dispatch   
◎ distribution of direct mail or a mail magazine, and other distribution (however, distribution can be stopped when seeming needlessness) of information considered to be advantageous to protecting profits to a member   
◎ a member -- the inquiry about the personal information from the person himself/herself 

* * *

**[Restriction of use]**  
I do not use a member's personal information for any uses other than the above-mentioned [purpose of use]. the case where it should use for uses other than [the purpose of use] -- a member -- I make a definite promise to obtain the consent of the person himself/herself. However, cases of the exception by regulation of Article 16 of the Act for Protection of Computer Processed Personal Data held by Administrative Organs, such as in the case of protection of the case where it is based on a statute, a life, or property etc., are excluded. 

* * *

**[The safety control of information, and the supervisor to an employee and a commission place]**  
A management representative is selected for a safety control and not only the employee of our company but the supervisor to a commission contractor carries out so that this fan club member's personal information may not be revealed. 

* * *

**[Restriction of third party offer]**  
I observe each above-mentioned item and do not disclose the personal information registered from you, members, for any third parties except for the case where it corresponds to following either.   
(1) a member -- the case where there is consent of the person himself/herself.   
(2) When personal information needs to be disclosed that the collection purpose specified to the member should be carried out to the cooperation company, tie-up company, and outsourcing company which have concluded our company and a nondisclosure agreement. (Example: Dispatch commission to commission contractors, such as products of our company, or product data, reference to the credit card company of the price clearing time, registration of the ticket by a concert sponsor, etc.)   
(3) When there is an inquiry from a member to this fan club and it is appropriate to perform a reply from the affiliated company and agency of our company according to the contents of a question.   
(4) When indicating in the state where member individuals, such as statistical data, are not discriminable. (Example: A request-for-information person's number etc.)   
(5) When it is able to ask for presentation based on a statute etc. 

[The correctness of information, and reference, correction and deletion / use stop]   
This fan club tries to secure a member's personal information correctly. being related with a member's personal information -- a member -- when the proposal of indication and correction when reference and information have an error etc. from the person himself/herself, deletion, and a use stop occurs, I correspond immediately. In that case, even this fan club needs to inform. in order to prevent disclosure of the personal information of the member to others -- these proposals -- a member -- as soon as that it is what is depended on the person himself/herself can check in our company, I do disclosure of personal information, correction, deletion, and a use stop within a rational period. 

* * *

**[Observance of the norm of a related statute and others]**  
This fan club observes the norm of the statute applied about the registered member personal information, and others. 

* * *

**[Change of a privacy policy]**  
Since this fan club protects certainly the personal information of you, members, he may reform a privacy policy with change of the statute of Japan, or other norms. In that case, I announce you at any time.
